RG 079:005, Department of Environmental Protection: Air, Waste and Water
Connecticut State Library
- Series 14. Bureau of Water Management, 1920-1979
  - Permitting, Enforcement, and Remediation Division, 1928-1979; bulk 1969-1977
    - Correspondence Files, 1997-050
      - Bridgeport (Box 6)
        - Standard Plating Works (Box 9)
        - Steve Buraway d/b/a Steve=s European Car Service (Box 9)
        - Sun Oil Co. Of Pennsylvania (Box 9)
        - Swan Engraving Co. (Box 9)
        - Szost’s Auto Sales, Inc. (Box 9)
        - Toral Motors, Inc. (Box 9)
        - Town Fair Tire Center of Bpt. (Box 9)
        - Turnpike Truck Repair Inc. (Box 9)
        - U-Haul/Boston Ave. Moving Center (Box 9)
        - UI/Bpt Harbor Station, 3 folders (Box 9)
        - UI/Steel Point Station, 3 folders (Box 9)
        - Universal Mfg. Corp. (Box 9)
        - Vertex Corp. (Box 9)
        - W & S Surgical Instrument Co. (Box 9)
        - Emanuel & Michael Musello d/b/a Waste Removal Inc. Of Bpt. (Box 9)
      - Bridgewater (Box 9)
        - Bridgewater Misc. (Box 9)
        - Bridgewater Siltation & Erosion (Box 9)
        - Bridgewater Burnham School (Box 9)
        - Sun Valley Farms (Box 9)
        - Topline Farm (Box 9)
        - Jackson S. Potter/Wintergreen Village, 3 folders (Box 9)
      - Bristol (Box 10)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 10)
        - Town of Bristol Oil Spill Reports (Box 10)
        - Bristol Landfill (Box 10)
        - Bristol/Middle Street Contaminated Wells (Box 10)
        - Bristol Siltation & Erosion (Box 10)
        - Bristol Subsurface Problems (Box 10)
        - Academy Auto Sales (Box 10)
        - Accurate Brass Corp (Box 10)
        - Accurate Forging Company (Box 10)
        - Acme Rivet & Machine, 3 folders (Box 10)
        - Armoloy Co. Of Connecticut (Box 10)
        - Associated Springs Corp/Wallace Barnes Div, 3 folders (Box 10)
        - Associated Springs Corp/Steel Div., 2 folders (Box 10)
        - Bedus & Stanke Electroplating (Box 10)
        - Bristol Auto (Box 10)
        - Bristol Brass Co., 2 folders (Box 10)
        - Bristol Chrome Co. (Box 10)
        - Bristol Ford, Inc. (Box 10)
        - Bristol Industries Corp (Box 10)
        - Bristol Water Dept. (Box 10)
        - David Butts & Max Borghesi (Box 10)
        - Castle & Sons Inc. (Box 10)
        - City National Printing (Box 10)
        - Collision Clinic of Connecticut (Box 10)
        - Connecticut Treatment Corp. (Box 10)
        - Doc’s Garage (Box 10)
        - The Endee Heat Treating Co. (Box 10)
        - Gavlick Machniery (Box 10)
        - Industrial Components Div., Inc. (Box 10)
        - Industrial Environmental Service Inc. Hearing (Box 10)
        - Industrial Environmental Service Inc. (Box 10)
        - J. H. Sessions & Son, 2 folders (Box 10)
        - J & S Metals Inc. (Box 10)
        - Jay’s Auto Center (Box 10)
        - Jerome’s Auto Service (Box 10)
        - W. A. Krueger Co. (Box 10)
        - Lee Spring Co. (Box 10)
        - Fred Miller Auto Body (Box 10)
        - Musumano Construction Co. (Box 10)
        - Quality Coils, Inc. (Box 11)
        - Riverside Motors Company (Box 11)
        - Speedy Muffler King (Box 11)
        - Stanley Industrial Components/Forestville (Box 11)
        - Stanley Plating Co./Forestville, 2 folders (Box 11)
        - Stephen Datsun (Proposed Site Map), 1977 (Box 11)
        - E C Tabora d/b/a Stop and Go Transmission (Box 11)
        - Superior Electric Company, 2 folders (Box 11)
        - Tilcon Tomasso/New Haven Trap Rock (Box 11)
        - Wasley Buick-Oldsmobile (Box 11)
      - Brookfield (Box 11)
        - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 11)
        - Brookfield Siltation & Erosion (Box 11)
        - Brookfield Subsurface Problems (Box 11)
        - Town of Brookfield Zoning Regulations (Box 11)
        - Rte 7 & Rt 25/Gasoline Problems (Box 11)
        - A. J. Tuck Company (Box 11)
        - Brookfield Condominiums (Box 11)
        - Brookfield Hills Assoc. (Box 11)
        - Brookfield Lanes/Proposed Bowling Center Site Rte 7 (Box 11)
        - Brookfield Power Equipment, Inc. (Box 11)
        - Caldors, Inc. (Box 11)
        - Country Walk, 2 folders (Box 11)
        - D.M. Engineering Inc. (Box 11)
        - Elmco/Emtek Station, 2 folders (Box 11)
        - Exxon Enterprises, Inc. (Box 11)
        - Friendly Ice Cream Corp. (Box 11)
        - G & D Auto Center, Inc. (Box 11)
        - Getty Service Station (Box 11)
        - Hearthstone Condos, 2 folders (Box 11)
        - High Meadow Apartments (Box 11)
        - High Meadow Apartments Report (Box 11)
        - Hoffman Farms, Inc. (Box 11)
        - Kent Sussex Shopping Center (Box 11)
        - Mobil Service Station (Box 11)
        - Mountain Glen Condominium (Box 11)
        - Newbury Crossing a/k/a/ Meetinghouse Village (Box 11)
        - New Milford Tractor Co., Inc. (Box 11)
        - Rapid Power Tech (Box 11)
        - Sandy Lake Village Assoc. (Box 11)
        - Teknicircuits, Inc. (Box 11)
        - Ultra-O-Ray Laundromat (Box 11)
      - Brooklyn (Box 12)
        - Brooklyn Misc, 2 folders (Box 12)
        - Arrow Hart, Inc. (Box 12)
        - Safeway Petroleum Inc. (Box 12)
        - Cyco Engineering (Box 12)
        - Brooklyn - Danielson Ford (Box 12)
        - Lucien Provost (Box 12)
        - Robert Sears (Box 12)
        - Salem Village Phase II (Box 12)
        - Steven Chesnowitz (Box 12)
      - Burlington (Box 12)
        - Burlington Misc., 2 folders (Box 12)
        - Burlington Subsurface Problems (Box 12)
        - Burlington Groundwater Contamination (Box 12)
        - Burlington Siltation & Erosion (Box 12)
        - Aiudi & Sons (Box 12)
        - Birch Ridge Subdivision, Investor’s Trust, inc. (Box 12)
        - Burlington Heights (Box 12)
        - CT Sand & Stone Corp. (Box 12)
        - Lake Gardan Co. (Box 12)
        - Speedy Muffler King Inc. (Box 12)
        - Woodcreek Subdivision (Box 12)
        - Woodponds Subdivision (Box 12)
      - Canaan (Box 12)
        - Canaan Misc., 2 folders (Box 12)
        - Canaan Town Sanitary Landfill (Box 12)
        - Canaan Subsurface Problems (Box 12)
        - Canaan Culligan Water Conditioning Co. (Box 12)
      - Canterbury (Box 12)
        - Canterbury Misc., 2 folders (Box 12)
        - Hill’s Body Shop (Box 12)
        - Sylvestri’s Auto Sales (Box 12)
        - Pollution of State Waterways (Box 12)
        - Tar Box Rd. (Box 12)
        - Little River Estates (Box 12)
        - Edward MacGlciflin (Box 12)
        - Maurice Levesque (Box 12)
        - Robert E. Owens (Box 12)
        - St. Augustine Church (Box 12)
        - Yaworski (Box 12)
      - Canton (Box 12)
        - Canton Subsurfac e Problems (Box 12)
        - Canton Misc, 2 folders (Box 12)
        - Canton Landfill (Box 12)
        - Canton Sewer Avoidance (Box 12)
        - Canton Siltation & Erosion (Box 12)
        - Canton East Hill & Gracy Rd. (Box 12)
        - Auto World Realty Ltd. (Box 12)
        - Bahre Corner Rd. (Box 12)
        - Clifton Condos (Box 12)
        - Cameron Lincoln-Mercury, 2 folders (Box 12)
        - Hollycrest Subdivision (Box 12)
        - Barry W. Holtman (Box 12)
      - Canton (Box 12)
        - Edward Herbert (Box 12)
        - Canton Land Development Co. (Box 12)
        - Canton Land Development Co. - Hearing, 3 folders (Box 12)
        - Stop & Go Gransmission (Box 12)
        - LaTrofforici Restaurant (Box 12)
        - MacDonald Plaza Muffler Shop (Box 13)
        - M Swift & Sons (Box 13)
        - Marilla Russell (Box 13)
        - Riley Tire & Brake (Box 13)
        - Chester Thomen (Box 13)
        - Woodland Acre (Box 13)
        - Woodchuck Hill Rd. (Box 13)
      - Chaplin (Box 13)
        - Chaplin Misc. (Box 13)
        - Imported Car Care of CT (Box 13)
      - Cheshire (Box 13)
        - Cheshire Misc., 2 folders (Box 13)
        - Cheshire Well Field Contamination (Box 13)
        - Cheshire Landfill (Box 13)
        - Allied Chemical Corp (Box 13)
        - Ball & Socket, 2 folders (Box 13)
        - Bovano of Cheshire (Box 13)
        - STP Cheshire Academy (Box 13)
        - STP Cheshire Correctional Center (Box 13)
        - Consolidated Industries, 2 folders (Box 13)
        - DOT Fasterner Co., 2 folders (Box 13)
        - Holgram Corp. - Hearing (Box 13)
        - Holgrath Corp (Box 13)
        - Marion Mfg. (Box 13)
        - Mazzella Restaurant (Box 13)
        - Meriden Water Dept. (Box 13)
        - Micro Tech (Box 13)
        - Shell (Box 13)
        - Siemens Corp., 2 folders (Box 13)
        - Raymond Sima (Box 13)
        - Waterbury Farrell Co., 2 folders (Box 13)
        - Jubilee Holding Co. (Box 13)
        - Cheshire Transmission Service (Box 13)
        - Skip’s Elmco Service (Box 13)
        - Willow Equipment Sales (Box 13)
        - C&Z Trailer Sales (Box 13)
        - Ace Truck Repair (Box 13)
      - Chester (Box 14)
        - Pioneer Products, Inc. (Box 14)
        - C.J. Bates & Son, 2 folders (Box 14)
        - Chester House (Box 14)
        - Deep River Sanitary Survey (Box 14)
        - James Goss (Box 14)
      - Clinton (Box 14)
        - Clinton Misc. (Box 14)
        - Clinton Garage Transfer Station (Box 14)
        - Clinton Refuse Disposal Area (Box 14)
        - Universal Wire Co. (Box 14)
        - Chesebruigh, Inc., 6 folders (Box 14)
        - Cedar Island Estates (Box 14)
        - Clinton Coi-Up Laundry (Box 14)
        - Tri-Town Tire Center (Box 14)
        - CT Water Co. (Box 14)
        - Suburbon Auto (Box 14)
        - Mal’s Auto & Truck Repair (Box 14)
        - Bill’s Harley-Davidson (Box 14)
        - DeFranks Restaurant (Box 14)
        - F. K. Construction Co. (Box 14)
        - Hammonassett Marina (Box 14)
        - National Sintered Alloys, Inc. (Box 14)
        - Rollar Gravel Pit (Box 14)
        - Bindloss Oil Co. (Box 14)
        - Stanley Bostitch Textron (Box 14)
        - CT Refining Co. (Box 14)
        - Stone Developers Inc., 2 folders (Box 14)
        - Valley Shore (Box 14)
      - Clinton (Box 15)
        - Victoria Monor, 4 folders (Box 15)
      - Colebrook (Box 15)
        - Colebrook Misc, 3 folders (Box 15)
        - Colebrook Siltration & Erosion (Box 15)
        - Rock Hall Estates (Box 15)
      - Colchester (Box 15)
        - Colchester Water Co. (Box 15)
        - EMH Associates, Inc. (Box 15)
        - Colchester Marshfield Manor (Box 15)
        - Modern Car Wash (Box 15)
        - Schuster Express, Inc. (Box 15)
        - Colchester Water Dept. (Box 15)
        - Colchester Misc (Box 15)
        - Standish Garage (Box 15)
        - Colchester Salvage, Inc. (Box 15)
        - Midway Motors (Box 15)
        - Wilson’s Auto Sales (Box 15)
      - Columbia (Box 15)
        - Columbia Misc, 2 folders (Box 15)
        - Columbia Lake (Box 15)
        - Columbia Landfill (Box 15)
        - Conklin Limestone (Box 15)
        - Drakes Blast Stripping Inc. (Box 15)
        - Francis Commissa Construction Co. (Box 15)
        - Hop River Septic Service, 2 folders (Box 15)
        - Hosmer Mountain Bottling Co., Inc. (Box 15)
        - Pine Hills II - Lot 26 (Box 15)
        - Superior Auto, Inc. (Box 15)
      - Cornwall (Box 15)
        - Cornwall Misc (Box 15)
        - Brookfield Chemical, Inc. (Box 15)
        - Thomas Byrness (Box 15)
      - Coventry (Box 16)
        - Coventry Misc. (Box 16)
        - Arrow Head Hidge Development, 2 folders (Box 16)
        - Coventry Municipal (Box 16)
        - CT Bi-Products (Box 16)
        - Proposed Community Development (Box 16)
        - Deknatel Division of Howmedia, Inc. (Box 16)
        - Angelo Demma (Box 16)
        - Desiato & Sanderson (Box 16)
        - Dep’sn Strip (Box 16)
        - Elm Water Co. (Box 16)
        - Frank L. Hastings (Box 16)
        - Hemlock Point (Box 16)
        - Jed Homes (Box 16)
        - Raymond Roman (Box 16)
        - Selfin Public Well (Box 16)
        - Sutures, Inc. (Box 16)
      - Cromwell (Box 16)
        - Cromwell Landfill (Box 16)
        - Rackcliffe Oil Co., Texaco, Inc. (Box 16)
        - Cromwell Misc. (Box 16)
        - The Car Store, Inc. (Box 16)
        - Rivergate Subdivision (Box 16)
        - The Ripley Co. (Box 16)
      - Danbury (Box 17)
        - Danbury Misc., 3 folders (Box 17)
        - Danbury Contaminated Well (Box 17)
        - Danbury Subsurface Problems (Box 17)
        - Danbury Siltation & Erosion (Box 17)
        - American Cyanamid Co. (Box 17)
        - Auto Electronics (Box 17)
        - Cardinals Auto Repair (Box 17)
        - Cleary’s Auto Service (Box 17)
        - Automotive Service (Box 17)
        - Dell’s Auto Wrecking Inc. (Box 17)
        - American Cyanamid (Box 17)
        - American Radionic Co., 2 folders (Box 17)
        - Amphenol R F Division Bunker-Ramo (Box 17)
        - Ball & Roller Beaning Co. (Box 17)
        - A. R. C. Construction (Box 17)
        - Bard - Parks (Box 17)
        - Beaver Brook Circuits (Box 17)
        - Bedoukian Research, Inc., 2 folders (Box 17)
        - Berol Products (Box 17)
        - Boehringer Ingelheim Ltd., 2 folders (Box 17)
        - Canzter Project (Box 17)
        - Caruso Prod. (Box 17)
        - Chayes Virginia Corp. (Box 17)
        - Chem-Tron Co. (Box 17)
        - Chevron USA Inc. (Box 17)
        - Columbia Diamond Ring Co. (Box 17)
        - Columbia Magnetics. (Box 17)
        - CT Waste Oil (Box 17)
        - Connor Inc., 3 folders (Box 17)
        - Danbury Metal Finishing Co. (Box 17)
        - Danbury Pavilion Health Care (Box 17)
        - Precision Mfg. (Box 17)
        - Printing & Litho, Inc. (Box 17)
        - David Estates (Ernie Hawley) (Box 17)
        - Design Circuits, Inc. - Hearing (Box 17)
        - Design Circuits, Inc., 2 folders (Box 17)
        - Electronics Metal Finishing Corp., 2 folders (Box 17)
        - Edward Sutt Assoc. (Box 17)
        - Fairfield Processing Corp. (Box 17)
        - R. J. Lallagher (Box 18)
        - Gar Electroforming Div. MTC Corp., 3 folders (Box 18)
        - General Data Com - Sand Pit Rd. Site (Box 18)
        - John W. Green & Sons (Box 18)
        - John F. Green & Fred Otto (Box 18)
        - Heli Coil Products, 2 folders (Box 18)
        - Danbury Instapak (Box 18)
        - Danbury J A N E (Box 18)
        - Jensen Trailer Park Well (Box 18)
        - Howard Johnson Restaurant (Box 18)
        - Kemeke, Inc. (Box 18)
        - LaPonti’s Auto (Box 18)
        - Marcus Dairy, Inc., 2 folders (Box 18)
        - Margerie Water Filtration, 2 folders (Box 18)
        - H. McLachlin & Co. (Box 18)
        - Medallic Art Co. (Box 18)
        - Menkes Development Corp. (Box 18)
        - Microtonics Corp. (Box 18)
        - Mosler Electronic System (Box 18)
        - National Can Corp., 2 folders (Box 18)
        - National Semiconductor Co. (Box 18)
        - Newmount Exploration Ltd. (Box 18)
        - C. D. Parks Co. (Box 18)
        - Perkin Elmer (Box 18)
        - Photronic Labs, Inc. (Box 18)
        - Pitney Bowes, Inc. (Box 18)
        - Qualitron Corp. (Box 18)
        - Republic Foil, 2 folders (Box 18)
        - Ridgemont Indus. Inc. (Box 18)
        - Gemini Auto Body, Inc. (Box 18)
        - Greco Trie, Inc. (Box 18)
        - Novella’s Wrecking Co. (Box 18)
        - Park Garage (Box 18)
        - Rocky’s Service Station, 2 folders (Box 18)
        - Danbury Misc. (Box 19)
        - Risdon Mfg. Co., 2 folders (Box 19)
        - Sealed Air Corp. (Box 19)
        - Dynamic Inc., Rust Lick, Inc. (Box 19)
        - Stop & Go Transmission, Inc. (Box 19)
        - U-Haul Midtown Moving (Box 19)
        - Ted’s Service Station (Box 19)
        - Lila J. Shaker (Box 19)
        - R. Williams Co. (Box 19)
        - City of Danbury Rest Area Project, 3 folders (Box 19)
        - C. D. Parks Co. (Box 19)
        - Technicircuits, Inc., 2 folders (Box 19)
        - Telesco Mason Supply (Box 19)
        - Union Carbide Corp. (Box 19)
        - USS Chemicals (Box 19)
        - Viking Wire Co., Inc. (Box 19)
        - West Lake Water Filtration Plant (Box 19)
        - Combustion Equipment Associates (Box 19)
      - Darien (Box 19)
        - Darien Landfill (Box 19)
        - Auto Center Inc. (Box 19)
        - Darien Equipment Corp. Assoc. (Box 19)
        - Noroton District (Box 19)
        - Furber Property (Box 19)
        - The Wee Burn Country Club, Inc. (Box 19)
      - Deep River (Box 19)
        - Deep river Misc. (Box 19)
        - Community Housing Assoc. (Box 19)
        - Esico, Inc. (Box 19)
        - Deep River Convalescent Home (Box 19)
        - Deep River Convalescent Hospital (Box 19)
        - Mount St. John School (Box 19)
        - Deep river Electric Soldering (Box 19)
        - Shorline Sand & Gravel Co. (Box 19)
        - UARCO, Inc., 2 folders (Box 19)
        - White Way Laundry (Box 19)
        - Blakeslee Arpaia Chapmen, Inc. (Box 19)
        - Town of Deep River (Box 19)
      - Derby (Box 20)
        - Derby Misc. (Box 20)
        - Town Fair Tire Center (Box 20)
        - Derby Auto Exchange Inc. (Box 20)
        - Housatonic River Dredging Project (Box 20)
        - City of Derby (Box 20)
        - Derby Landfill (Box 20)
        - W. E. Bassett Co. (Box 20)
        - A. W. Beard Construction Corp. (Box 20)
        - Belleview Drive Well Problems (Box 20)
        - Derby Sponge Products, Inc. (Box 20)
        - Derby Sand & Asphalt (Box 20)
        - B. F. Goodrich products (Box 20)
        - Hill Dye & Print Works, 4 folders (Box 20)
        - Industrial Heal Treating (Box 20)
        - Manger Die Casting Co., Inc. (Box 20)
        - 3M Co. (Box 20)
        - United Illuminating, 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Durham (Box 20)
        - Durham Misc. (Box 20)
        - Durham Landfill (Box 20)
        - Durham Firehouse (Box 20)
        - Henry Bugai (Box 20)
        - Durham Convalescent Home (Box 20)
        - Camps Tavern (Box 20)
        - Durham High School (Box 20)
        - Durham Surface Plans & Review (Box 20)
        - Stahl’s Corner, Inc. (Box 20)
        - Durham Mfg. Co. (Box 20)
        - Henry Simon (Box 20)
        - Twin Maples Nursing (Box 20)
        - Raymond Wimler (Box 20)
        - Parson Co., W. A. Inc., 2 folders (Box 20)
        - Richard Vynalek (Box 20)
      - Eastford (Box 21)
        - Eastford Misc. (Box 21)
      - East Granby (Box 21)
        - East Granby Misc. (Box 21)
        - East Granby Subsurface Problems (Box 21)
        - ACI Inc. (Box 21)
        - East Granby Oil Spill Reports (Box 21)
        - Culbro Co. (Box 21)
        - Barnhart, Johnson, Francis & Wild (Medical Bldg) (Box 21)
        - Delta Industries/Thiokol Chemical-Delta Div. (Box 21)
        - Griffith Laboratories (Box 21)
        - Julian Precision Ball Corp. (Box 21)
        - Magnolech - The DSD Co. (Box 21)
        - Rockbestos Co. (Box 21)
        - William H. Wilson Apt., 2 folders (Box 21)
      - East Haddam (Box 21)
        - East Haddam Misc (Box 21)
        - Becket Academy (Box 21)
        - Brownell & Co., 3 folders (Box 21)
        - Robert Cone (Box 21)
        - Champion House (Box 21)
        - Granada Hill Farm (Box 21)
        - H. R. Eng. Inc. (Box 21)
        - H. R. Eng. Labs Inc. (Box 21)
        - Lake Hayward (Box 21)
        - Stanley Lesick (Box 21)
        - Donald Meyer (Box 21)
        - Mortimer A. Gelston (Box 21)
        - Orchard Mansion (Box 21)
        - Pioneer Products Inc., 4 folders (Box 21)
        - Total Disposal System (Box 21)
        - Williams Chevrolet, Inc. (Box 21)
      - East Hampton (Box 22)
        - East Hampton Misc, 2 folders (Box 22)
        - Advanced Automotive Repair (Box 22)
        - East Hampton Outfall Sewer (Box 22)
        - Town of East Hampton (Box 22)
        - American Distilling & Mfg. Co., Inc. (Box 22)
        - Belltown Village (Box 22)
        - Bevin Brothers Mfg., 3 folders (Box 22)
        - Chatham Inn STP (Box 22)
        - John Dill (Box 22)
        - East Hampton High School (Box 22)
        - East Hampton Laundromat (Box 22)
        - Electric Metals, Inc. (Box 22)
        - Food Bag, Inc. (Box 22)
        - Henry’s Lawn Mower Service (Box 22)
        - Lake Pocotopaug (Sanitary Survey), 2 folders (Box 22)
        - L & W Plating Co., 3 folders (Box 22)
        - Modern Auto Body & Used Car Sales (Box 22)
        - P.& M Cycle (Box 22)
        - Pressure-Pak, Inc., 4 folders (Box 22)
        - #20 Quality Survey (Box 22)
      - East Hartford (Box 22)
        - East Hartford Misc., 2 folders (Box 22)
        - East Hartford Town of (Box 22)
        - East Hartford Municipal Incinerators (Box 22)
        - East Hartford Municipal Landfill (Box 22)
        - Arrow Line (Box 22)
        - Automatic Comfort Corp. (Box 22)
        - A Leitao’s Minit Car Wash Inc. (Box 22)
        - Burnside Co. (Box 22)
        - Brown St Sewer Housing Project (Box 22)
        - Burnside Paper Company (Box 22)
        - Case Brothers (Box 23)
        - C & M Warehouse, Inc. (Box 23)
        - Cellu Projects, 4 folders (Box 23)
        - Century Color Labs (Box 23)
        - The Clobber Shop (Box 23)
        - CT Truck & Trailer Co. (Box 23)
        - Contromatics Corp. (Box 23)
        - Crestwood Products Corp (Box 23)
        - Crestwood Products Corp/Hearing (Box 23)
        - Culligan Water Treatment, 2 folders (Box 23)
        - Dan’s Auto Body (Box 23)
        - Exxon Co. (Box 23)
        - Finast (Box 23)
        - Fotomat (Box 23)
        - Fotolabs (Box 23)
        - Fotomat Labs (Box 23)
        - General Oil Co. (Box 23)
        - Glenbrook Swim Club, Inc. (Box 23)
        - Golden Custom Inc. (Box 23)
        - Harper Buffing Machine, 2 folders (Box 23)
        - Hydro Honing Lab, Inc. (Box 23)
        - Imported Auto Service of East Hartford (Box 23)
        - Kaveckas Automotive, Inc. (Box 23)
        - Liberty Oil Equipment Co. (Box 23)
        - Lomac, Inc. (Box 23)
        - Longo Tire (Box 23)
        - McCauley Enterprise/Esposite-Volpe (Box 23)
        - Mechanic Uniform Service (Box 23)
        - Melly’s Service Station (Box 23)
        - New England Chrome Plating Co., 2 folders (Box 23)
        - Northern Trucking Equipment, 2 folders (Box 23)
        - Newman Lincoln Mercury (Box 23)
        - Nutmeg Auto Body (Box 23)
        - Parker X Ray (Box 23)
        - Pilot Co. (Box 23)
        - Pratt & Whitney Aircraft, 8 folders (Box 24)
        - P.T. Auto Repair (Box 24)
        - Ramada Inn, Inc. (Box 24)
        - Republic Steel Corp (Box 24)
        - St. Mary’s Elderly Apts. (Box 24)
        - Shell Oil Co. (Box 24)
        - Sun Oil Co. (Box 24)
        - Texaco Inc. (Box 24)
        - Texaco Oil (Box 24)
        - Tolland Enterprises, Inc. (Box 24)
        - Towsend Ind. (Box 24)
        - Willow Arms Assoc. (Box 24)
        - Yankee Auto/Rustproof (Box 24)
        - Yankee Kenworth (Box 24)
      - East Haven (Box 24)
        - East Haven Misc (Box 24)
        - East Haven Associates (Box 24)
        - East Haven Highway Auto Sales (Box 24)
        - Arc Construction (Box 24)
        - Farm River Motors (Box 24)
        - New Haven Water Co., 2 folders (Box 24)
        - New Haven Truck & Auto Body, Inc. (Box 24)
      - East Lyme (Box 25)
        - East Lyme Misc, 2 folders (Box 25)
        - East Lyme Municipal (Box 25)
        - CT Corretional Institution (Box 25)
        - CT State Farm For Women (Box 25)
        - DeBartolos Service, Inc. (Box 25)
        - Fazzino Prop. (Box 25)
        - Jasper N. Green (Box 25)
        - E. Lyme Co. & Howard Johnson of Boston, 3 folders (Box 25)
        - Golden Spur Motel (Box 25)
        - Laurel Hill Acres, Inc. (Box 25)
        - Main St. Laundromat (Box 25)
        - Maxwell Marston (Box 25)
        - Muriel Chaplin (Box 25)
        - Morton House (Box 25)
        - Niantic Car Wash (Box 25)
        - Niantic Grill (Box 25)
        - Pappas Laundromat (Box 25)
        - Pataganset Finishing Co., Inc. (Box 25)
        - Patriia Moreau (Box 25)